First comes love. Then comes chaos.
A Nice Indian Boy is a romance, comedy film directed by Roshan Sethi.
When Naveen brings his fiancé Jay home to meet his traditional Indian family, they must contend with accepting
his white-orphan-artist boyfriend and helping them plan the Indian wedding of their dreams.
Naveen Gavaskar, played by Karan Soni.
Jay Kurundkar, played by Jonathan Groff.
Arundhathi Gavaskar, played by Sunita Mani.
Megha Gavaskar, played by Zarna Garg.
Archit Gavaskar, played by Harish Patel.
Paul, played by Peter S. Kim.
A Nice Indian Boy is a 2025 American romantic
comedy film directed by Roshan Sethi.
Based on Madhuri Shekar's play of the same name, the film follows Naveen, an Indian-American doctor, who
brings his fiancé, Jay, a white man adopted by Indian parents, to meet his traditional family.
It stars Karan Soni, Jonathan Groff, Sunita Mani, Zarna Garg, and Harish Patel.
The film premiered at South by Southwest on March 12, 2024, and was released
in the US on April 4, 2025, by Blue Harbor Entertainment.
The film explores themes of coming out, interracial
romance, lgbt, gay romance, traditional family.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.